A Guide to the International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC) records FA084
Rockefeller Archive Center
- IBEC Microforms, J; 135 Reels
  - IHC PR-IBEC Housing Co. Inc.: Puerto Rico: Reports-Housing Market-N. E.-Puerto Rico (Card 200-20-(01-03))
  - IHC PR-IBEC Housing Co. Inc.: Puerto Rico: Reports-Mgmt-Services Industry (Card 200-20-(01-02))
  - IHC PR-IBEC Housing Co. Inc.: Puerto Rico: Reports-Villa Marista Land Use (Card 200-20-01)
  - IHCORP: El Salvador: Reports-Better Health for People (Card 233-20-(01-02))
    File Code should begin with 2033
  - IHCORP: El Salvador: Reports-Mejor Slaud Para El Pueblo (Card 233-20-(01-03))
  - IHCORP: El Salvador: Reports-San Miguel-Plan Regulado (Card 233-20-(01-02))
  - IHCORP: El Salvador: Reports-Valle De Esperanza-New Life (Card 233-20-(01-02))
  - IHCORP: El Salvador: Reports-Valle De Esperanza-Nueva Vida (Card 233-20-(01-03))
  - IHCORP: El Salvador: Reports-Valle De Esperanza-Plan Desarollo (Card 233-20-(01-02))
  - IHCORP: Iran: Reports-Khuzastan Region- D & R Report #1 (Card 233-20-01)
  - IHCORP: Iran: Reports-Khuzastan Region- D & R Report #2 (Card 233-20-01)
  - IHCORP: Iran: Reports-Khuzastan Region- D & R Report #3 (Card 233-20-01)
  - IHCORP: Iran: Reports-Khuzastan Region- D & R Report #4 (Card 233-20-01)
  - IHCORP: Iraq: Projects-Low Cost Housing Study (Card 2033-16-(01-02))
  - IHCORP: Iraq: Projects-Officer Housing AssociationLimited (Card 2033-16-01)
  - IHCORP: Iraq: Projects-Middle East-Housing for Middle East (Card 2033-16-01)
  - IHCORP: Report- Urban Vulnerability in Atomic Age (Card 2033-20-01)
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): Florida (Margate Properties): Insurance (Reel J-120, Card 751-09)
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): Florida (Margate Properties): Legal (Reel J-119, Card 751-11-(01-35))
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): Florida (Margate Properties): Legal-Bateman, Frank (Litigation) (Reel J-119, Card 751-11)
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): Florida (Margate Properties): Legal-Dames & Moore (Reel J-119, Card 751-11-(01-05))
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): Florida (Margate Properties): Legal-Dames & Moore (Reel J-120)
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): Florida (Margate Properties): Legal-Documents (Reel J-119, Card 751-11-(01-03))
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): Florida (Margate Properties): Legal-McGeary, John H., Jr. (Reel J-120, Card 751-11-(01-02))
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): Florida (Margate Properties): Office (Reel J-120, Card 751-12)
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): Florida (Margate Properties): Planning-Utilities-Margate Utilities Corporation (Reel J-120, Card 751-14-(01-06))
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): Florida (Margate Properties): Property-IBEC Club (Reel J-120, Card 751-17-(01-06))
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): Florida (Margate Properties): Publicity (Reel J-120, Card 751-19)
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): Florida (Margate Properties): Reports (Reel J-120, Card 751-20)
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): New York: Conference (Reel J-121, Card 750-04-(01-02))
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): New York: Finance (Reel J-121, Card 750-07-(01-13))
    750-07-02, Two cards
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): New York: Finance-Loans- Chase Manhattan Bank (Reel J-121, Card 750-07-(01-04))
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): New York: Finance-Loans-Chase-Chile (Reel J-121, Card 750-07)
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): New York: Finance-Loans-Chase-Iran (Reel J-121, Card 750-07-(01-02))
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): New York: Finance-Loans-Chase-MDC-Royal Palm (Reel J-121, Card 750-07-(01-02))
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): New York: Finance-Loans-Chase-MDC- Villa Contessa (Reel J-121, Card 750-07-(01-03))
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): New York: Finance-Loans-Chase-PKDC (Parkville Development Corporation) (Reel J-121, Card 750-07)
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): New York: Finance-Loans-Chase-Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Reel J-121, Card 750-07)
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): New York: Finance-Loans-Chase-Ruiz Soler (Reel J-121, Card 750-07)
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): New York: Finance-Loans-Chase-TDC (Tana Development Corporation) (Reel J-121, Card 750-07-(01-04))
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): New York: Finance-Loans-Chase-Villa Del Rey (Reel J-121, Card 750-07-(01-03))
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): New York: Finance-Statements (Reel J-121, Card 750-07-01)
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): New York: Insurance (Reel J-121, Card 750-09)
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): New York: Insurance-Chile (Reel J-121, Card 750-09-(01-02))
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): New York: Insurance-Government-All Risk (Reel J-122, Card 750-09-(01-05))
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): New York: Insurance-Iran (Reel J-121, Card 750-09-(01-02))
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): New York: Insurance-Iran (Reel J-122)
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): New York: Insurance-Iran-Claims (Reel J-122, Card 750-09-(01-02))
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): New York: Insurance-Peru (Reel J-122, Card 750-09)
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): New York: Insurance-Puerto Rico (Reel J-122, Card 750-09-(01-05))
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): New York: Insurance-Puerto Rico-Claims (Reel J-122, Card 750-09-(01-02))
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): New York: Investments (Reel J-122, Card 750-10)
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): New York: Legal (Reel J-122, Card 750-11-(01-06))
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): New York: Legal-Government Regulations-Lobbying (Reel J-122, Card 750-11)
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): New York: Legal-Government Regulations - S.1478 & S.582 (Reel J-122, Card 750-11-(01-04))
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): New York: Legal-Patents-Billner, Karl P. (Reel J-122, Card 750-11-(01-03))
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): New York: Planning-Expansions-Mobile Homes (Reel J-122, Card 750-14-(01-02))
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): New York: Property-Equipment (Reel J-122, Card 750-17)
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): New York: Publicity (Reel J-123, Card 750-19-(01-03))
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): New York: Publicity-Argentina (Reel J-123, Card 750-19)
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): New York: Publicity-Chile (Reel J-123, Card 750-19)
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): New York: Publicity-Peru (Reel J-123, Card 750-19)
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): New York: Reports-Chile-Sales (Reel J-122, Card 750-20-(01-02))
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): New York: Reports-Iran-Sales (Reel J-122, Card 750-20)
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): New York: Reports-Peru-Progress (Reel J-122, Card 750-20)
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): New York: Reports-Peru-Sales (Reel J-122, Card 750-20-(01-03))
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): New York: Reports-Puerto Rico-Sales (Reel J-122, Card 750-20-(01-02))
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): New York: Staff-Consultants-Foley, R.M. (Reel J-122, Card 750-22-(01-06))
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): New York: Staff-Consultants-Foley, R.M. (Reel J-123)
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): New York: Staff-Consultants-Foley Reports (Reel J-123, Card 750-22)
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): Peru: Credit (Reel J-118, Card 753-05-(01-02))
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): Peru: Finance (Reel J-118, Card 753-07-(01-06))
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): Peru: Legal (Reel J-118, Card 753-11-(01-02))
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): Peru: Office (Reel J-118, Card 753-12-(01-03))
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): Peru: Publicity (Reel J-118, Card 753-19)
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): Peru-Salamanca: Finance (Reel J-118, Card 753-07-(01-26))
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): Peru-Salamanca: Finance (Reel J-119)
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): Peru-Salamanca: Finance-Budgets-Construction (Reel J-119, Card 753-07-(01-02))
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): Peru-Salamanca: Finance-AID Guarantees (Reel J-119, Card 753-07-(01-06))
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): Peru-Salamanca: Finance-Reports (Reel J-119, Card 753-07-(01-02))
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): Peru-Salamanca: Legal (Reel J-119, Card 753-11-(01-02))
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): Peru-Salamanca: Office (Reel J-119, Card 753-12)
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): Peru-Salamanca: Planning-Specifications (Reel J-119, Card 753-14-(01-02))
  - IBEC Housing Division (IHD): Peru-Salamanca: Property (Reel J-119, Card 753-17-(01-03))
  - ILAPECA: Venezuela: Competition (Reel J-24, Card 1302-03)
    ILAPECA (Industrias Lacteas de Perija C. A.)
  - ILAPECA: Venezuela: Directors (Reel J-23, Card 1302-06-(01-03))
  - ILAPECA: Venezuela: Finance (Reel J-22, Card 1302-07-(01-42))
    1302-07-03, Two cards
  - ILAPECA: Venezuela: Finance (Reel J-23)
  - ILAPECA: Venezuela: Finance-Guarantees (Card 1302-07-(01-02))
  - ILAPECA: Venezuela: Incorporation (Reel J-23, Card 1302-08-(01-02))
  - ILAPECA: Venezuela: Legal (Reel J-23, Card 1302-11-(01-10))
  - ILAPECA: Venezuela: Organization (Reel J-23, Card 1302-13)
  - ILAPECA: Venezuela: Planning (Reel J-23, Card 1302-14)
  - ILAPECA: Venezuela: Property (Reel J-23, Card 1302-17-(01-02))
  - ILAPECA: Venezuela: Publicity (Reel J-24, Card 1302-19-(01-02))
  - ILAPECA: Venezuela: Reports (Reel J-24, Card 1302-20)
  - ILAPECA: Venezuela: Staff (Reel J-24, Card 1302-22-(01-03))
  - ILAPECA: Venezuela: Stockholders (Reel J-24, Card 1302-23)
  - Industrial Mining Development Bank of Iran (IMDBI): Finance (Reel J-130, Card 1512-07-(01-19))
  - Industrial Mining Development Bank of Iran (IMDBI): Legal (Reel J-130, Card 1512-11-(01-04))
  - Industrial Mining Development Bank of Iran (IMDBI): Legal (Reel J-131)
  - IBEC Management Services, Inc. (IMS): Argentine Branch: Finance (Reel J-24, Card 775-07-(01-08))
  - IBEC Management Services, Inc. (IMS): Argentine Branch: Legal (Reel J-25, Card 775-11-(01-02))
  - IBEC Management Services, Inc. (IMS): Argentine Branch: Staff (Reel J-25, Card 775-22)
  - IBEC Management Services, Inc. (IMS): Chilean Branch: Finance (Reel J-25, Card 774-07-(01-11))
  - IBEC Management Services, Inc. (IMS): Chilean Branch: Legal (Reel J-25, Card 774-11-(01-02))
  - IBEC Management Services, Inc. (IMS): Chilean Branch: Property (Reel J-25, Card 774-17)
  - IBEC Management Services, Inc. (IMS): Chilean Branch: Publicity (Reel J-25, Card 774-19)
  - IBEC Management Services, Inc. (IMS): Chilean Branch: Reports (Reel J-25, Card 774-20-(01-02))
  - IBEC Management Services, Inc. (IMS): Chilean Branch: Staff (Reel J-25, Card 774-17)
    Mislabeled-Staff-22
  - IBEC Management Services, Inc. (IMS): Colombian Branch: Capitalization-Reg. (Reel J-25, Card 773-02)
  - IBEC Management Services, Inc. (IMS): Colombian Branch: Finance (Reel J-25, Card 773-07-(01-11))
  - IBEC Management Services, Inc. (IMS): Colombian Branch: Finance-Debt Reg. (Card 773-07-(01-07))
  - IBEC Management Services, Inc. (IMS): Colombian Branch: Finance-Disbursements (Card 773-07)
  - IBEC Management Services, Inc. (IMS): Colombian Branch: Legal (Reel J-25, Card 773-11-(01-04))
  - IBEC Management Services, Inc. (IMS): Colombian Branch: Public Relations (Reel J-25, Card 773-18)
  - IBEC Management Services, Inc. (IMS): Colombian Branch: Publicity (Reel J-25, Card 773-19)
  - IBEC Management Services, Inc. (IMS): Colombian Branch: Reports (Reel J-25, Card 773-20)
  - IBEC Management Services, Inc. (IMS): Colombian Branch: Staff (Reel J-25, Card 773-22-(01-02))
  - IBEC Management Services, Inc. (IMS): Delaware: Directors (Reel J-24, Card 770-06)
  - IBEC Management Services, Inc. (IMS): Delaware: Finance (Reel J-24, Card 770-07-(01-06))
  - IBEC Management Services, Inc. (IMS): Delaware: Legal (Reel J-24, Card 770-11)
  - IBEC Management Services, Inc. (IMS): Delaware: Legal-Power of Attorney (Card 770-11-(01-05))
  - IBEC Management Services, Inc. (IMS): Delaware: Planning-Brazil Br (Reel J-24, Card 770-14-(01-02))
  - IBEC Management Services, Inc. (IMS): Delaware: Reports (Reel J-24, Card 770-20)
  - IBEC Management Services, Inc. (IMS): Delaware: Staff (Reel J-24, Card 770-22)
  - IBEC Management Services, Inc. (IMS): Peruvian Branch: Finance (Reel J-26, Card 780-07-(01-10))
  - IBEC Management Services, Inc. (IMS): Peruvian Branch: Finance-Cash Flow (Card 780-07)
  - IBEC Management Services, Inc. (IMS): Peruvian Branch: Legal (Reel J-26, Card 780-11-(01-03))
  - IBEC Management Services, Inc. (IMS): Peruvian Branch: Public Relations (Reel J-26, Card 780-18)
  - IBEC Management Services, Inc. (IMS): Peruvian Branch: Reports (Reel J-26, Card 780-20)
  - IBEC Management Services, Inc. (IMS): Peruvian Branch: Staff (Reel J-26, Card 780-22)
  - IBEC Management Services, Inc. (IMS): Venezuelan Branch: Finance (Card 772-07-(01-09))
  - IBEC Management Services, Inc. (IMS): Venezuelan Branch: Legal (Card 772-11-(01-02))
  - IBEC Management Services, Inc. (IMS): Venezuelan Branch: Public Relations (Card 772-18)
  - IBEC Management Services, Inc. (IMS): Venezuelan Branch: Staff (Card 772-22)
  - Incredit S. A.: Finance (Reel J-16, Card 953-07-(01-07))
    Incredit S. A. (Financiaciones Industriales Incredit S.A.)
  - Incredit S. A.: Finance-Disbursements (Card 953-07)
  - Indusquima S.A.I.C.: Brazil: Credit, 1969 (Reel J-27, Card 154-05)
  - Indusquima S.A.I.C.: Brazil: Directors (Reel J-28, Card 154-06)
  - Indusquima S.A.I.C.: Brazil: Finance, 1969 (Reel J-27, Card 154-07-(01-35))
  - Indusquima S.A.I.C.: Brazil: Incorporation (Reel J-28, Card 154-08)
  - Indusquima S.A.I.C.: Brazil: Legal (Reel J-28, Card 154-11-(01-03))
  - Indusquima S.A.I.C.: Brazil: Organization (Reel J-28, Card 154-13)
  - Indusquima S.A.I.C.: Brazil: Planning-Expansion-Chile (Reel J-28, Card 154-14-(01-04))
  - Indusquima S.A.I.C.: Brazil: Publicity (Reel J-28, Card 154-19)
  - Indusquima S.A.I.C.: Brazil: Reports (Reel J-28, Card 154-20-(01-04))
  - Indusquima S.A.I.C.: Brazil: Reports-Feasibility (Card 154-20)
  - Indusquima S.A.I.C.: Brazil: Staff (Reel J-28, Card 154-22)
  - Indusquima S.A.I.C.: Brazil: Stockholders (Reel J-28, Card 154-23)
  - Industrial Finance Corp. of Thailand (IFC): Finance (Reel J-55, Card 1529-07-(01-05))
  - Industrial Finance Corp. of Thailand (IFC): Finance-CIIC Papers (Reel J-55, Card 1529-07)
  - Inlaca: Competition (Reel J-20, Card 1303-03)
    Inlaca (C. A. Industria Lactea de Carabobo)
  - Inlaca: Directors (Reel J-20, Card 1303-06-(01-10))
  - Inlaca: Finance (Reel J-18, Card 1303-07-(01-75))
  - Inlaca: Finance (Reel J-19)
  - Inlaca: Finance (Reel J-20)
  - Inlaca: Finance-Maldonado Group (Card 1303-07-(01-11))
  - Inlaca: Incorporation (Reel J-20, Card 1303-08-(01-04))
  - Inlaca: Legal (Reel J-20, Card 1303-11-(01-06))
  - Inlaca: Legal-Foremost Agreement (Card 1303-11)
  - Inlaca: Legal-Golden State Agreement (Card 1303-11-(01-02))
  - Inlaca: Legal-Labor Contract (Card 1303-11)
  - Inlaca: Legal-Management Contract (Card 1303-11-(01-02))
  - Inlaca: Legal-Producers Contract (Card 1303-11-(01-02))
  - Inlaca: Legal-Technical Assistant Agreement (Card 1303-11-(01-02))
  - Inlaca: Organization (Reel J-20, Card 1303-13-(01-02))
  - Inlaca: Planning (Reel J-20, Card 1303-14-(01-04))
  - Inlaca: Property (Reel J-20, Card 1303-17-(01-14))
  - Inlaca: Property (Reel J-21)
  - Inlaca: Publicity (Reel J-20, Card 1303-19-(01-02))
  - Inlaca: Reports (Reel J-21, Card 1303-20-(01-10))
  - Inlaca: Reports-Market Study by Beach (Card 1303-20-(01-03))
  - Inlaca: Reports-Study of Operations (Card 1303-20-(01-02))
  - Inlaca: Reports-Study of Operations-Finance (Card 1303-20-(01-02))
  - Inlaca: Staff (Reel J-21, Card 1303-22-(01-05))
  - Inlaca: Stockholders (Reel J-20, Card 1303-23-(01-04))
  - IBEC-RBH (Rollins Burdick Hunter S. A.): Argentina: Competition (Reel J-6, Card 440-03)
  - IBEC-RBH (Rollins Burdick Hunter S. A.): Argentina: Directors (Reel J-6, Card 440-06-(01-02))
  - IBEC-RBH (Rollins Burdick Hunter S. A.): Argentina: Finance (Reel J-6, Card 440-07-(01-13))
  - IBEC-RBH (Rollins Burdick Hunter S. A.): Argentina: Finance-Disbursements (Card 440-07)
  - IBEC-RBH (Rollins Burdick Hunter S. A.): Argentina: Incorporation (Card 440-08-(01-03))
  - IBEC-RBH (Rollins Burdick Hunter S. A.): Argentina: Legal (Reel J-6, Card 440-11)
  - IBEC-RBH (Rollins Burdick Hunter S. A.): Argentina: Planning (Reel J-6, Card 440-14)
  - IBEC-RBH (Rollins Burdick Hunter S. A.): Argentina: Publicity (Reel J-6, Card 440-19)
  - IBEC-RBH (Rollins Burdick Hunter S. A.): Argentina: Reports (Reel J-6, Card 440-20-(01-03))
  - IBEC-RBH (Rollins Burdick Hunter S. A.): Argentina: Staff (Reel J-6, Card 440-22-(01-02))
  - IBEC-RBH (Rollins Burdick Hunter S. A.): Argentina: Stockholders (Reel J-6, Card 440-23)
  - IBEC AA (Arbor Acres) Argentina S. A.: Directors (Reel J-59, Card 830-06)
  - IBEC AA (Arbor Acres) Argentina S. A.: Finance (Reel J-59, Card 830-07-(01-10))
  - IBEC AA (Arbor Acres) Argentina S. A.: Finance (Card 830-07)
    Blank Sleeve
  - IBEC AA (Arbor Acres) Argentina S. A.: Finance-Disbursements (Reel J-60, Card 830-07-(01-16))
    830-07-01, Two cards. One card labeled 830-02.
  - IBEC AA (Arbor Acres) Argentina S. A.: Finance-Roberts SA & Morgan Guaranty Transaction (Reel J-60, Card 830-07-(01-02))
  - IBEC AA (Arbor Acres) Argentina S. A.: Finance-Royalties (Reel J-60, Card 830-07)
  - IBEC AA (Arbor Acres) Argentina S. A.: Incorporation (Reel J-59, Card 830-08)
  - IBEC AA (Arbor Acres) Argentina S. A.: Insurance (Reel J-60, Card 830-09)
  - IBEC AA (Arbor Acres) Argentina S. A.: Legal (Reel J-59, Card 830-11-(01-04))
  - IBEC AA (Arbor Acres) Argentina S. A.: Legal-Contracts-Albayda (Reel J-59, Card 830-11-(01-02))
  - IBEC AA (Arbor Acres) Argentina S. A.: Legal-Contracts-Willis-Etc (Reel J-59, Card 830-11)
  - IBEC AA (Arbor Acres) Argentina S. A.: Publicity (Reel J-60, Card 830-19)
  - IBEC AA (Arbor Acres) Argentina S. A.: Reports (Reel J-59, Card 830-20-(01-03))
  - IBEC AA (Arbor Acres) Argentina S. A.: Reports-Feasibility (Reel J-59, Card 830-20)
  - IBEC AA (Arbor Acres) Argentina S. A.: Staff (Reel J-59, Card 830-22-(01-02))
  - IBEC-Bland Construction Corp.: Puerto Rico: Finance (Card 924-07-(01-03))
  - IBEC-Bland Construction Corp.: Puerto Rico: Incorporation (Card 924-08-01)
  - IBEC-Bland Construction Corp.: Puerto Rico: Legal (Card 924-11-01)
  - IBEC-Bland Construction Corp.: Puerto Rico: Projects (Card 924-16-(01-02))
  - IBEC-Bland Construction Corp.: Puerto Rico: Projects-Caribe Hilton (Card 924-16-01)
  - IBEC-Bland Construction Corp.: Puerto Rico: Projects-Caguas Hospital (Card 924-16-01)
  - IBEC-Bland Construction Corp.: Puerto Rico: Projects-Condominiums (Card 924-16-01)
  - IBEC-Bland Construction Corp.: Puerto Rico: Projects-Government Center (Card 924-16-01)
  - IBEC-Bland Construction Corp.: Puerto Rico: Projects-Industial Building-Antilles (Card 924-16-01)
  - IBEC-Bland Construction Corp.: Puerto Rico: Projects-Pdizer-Jacobs (Card 924-16-01)
  - IBEC-Bland Construction Corp.: Puerto Rico: Projects-Ramey Jr-Sr High School (Card 924-16-01)
  - IBEC-Bland Construction Corp.: Puerto Rico: Projects-Rockresorts (Card 924-16-(01-02))
  - IBEC-Bland Construction Corp.: Puerto Rico: Projects-Sea-Land (Card 924-16-01)
  - IBEC-Bland Construction Corp.: Puerto Rico: Publicity (Card 924-19-01)
  - IBEC-Bland Construction Corp.: Puerto Rico: Reports (Card 924-20-01)
  - IBEC-Bland Construction Corp.: Puerto Rico: Staff (Card 924-22-01)
  - IBEC Branch: Argentina: Finance (Reel J-57, Card 704-07-(01-12))
  - IBEC Branch: Argentina: Finance-Boote & Company (Reel J-57, Card 704-07)
  - IBEC Branch: Argentina: Finance-Disbursements (Reel J-57, Card 704-07)
  - IBEC Branch: Argentina: Insurance (Reel J-57, Card 704-09)
  - IBEC Branch: Argentina: Staff (Reel J-57, Card 704-22)
  - IBEC Branch: Peru: Finance (Reel J-57, Card 701-07-(01-09))
  - IBEC Branch: Peru: Finance (Reel J-58)
  - IBEC Branch: Peru: Insurance (Reel J-57, Card 701-09)
  - IBEC Branch: Peru: Legal (Reel J-57, Card 701-11-(01-03))
  - IBEC Branch: Peru: Office (Reel J-57, Card 701-12)
  - IBEC Branch: Peru: Public Relations (Reel J-57, Card 701-18)
  - IBEC Branch: Peru: Reports (Reel J-57, Card 701-20)
  - IBEC Branch: Peru: Staff (Reel J-57, Card 701-22)
  - IBEC Branch: Puerto Rico: Competition (Reel J-93, Card 708-03-(01-04))
  - IBEC Branch: Puerto Rico: Finance (Reel J-95, Card 708-07-(01-16))
  - IBEC Branch: Puerto Rico: Finance-Sale- Supermarkets (Operations) to Grand Union (Reel J-95, Card 708-07-(01-08))
  - IBEC Branch: Puerto Rico: Insurance (Reel J-95, Card 708-09-(01-05))
  - IBEC Branch: Puerto Rico: Legal (Reel J-95, Card 708-11-(01-04))
  - IBEC Branch: Puerto Rico: Legal-Blanco Lugo, Luis (Claims) (Reel J-95, Card 708-11-(01-17))
  - IBEC Branch: Puerto Rico: Legal-Blanco Lugo, Luis (Claims) (Reel J-96)
  - IBEC Branch: Puerto Rico: Legal-Lopez Case (Reel J-96, Card 708-11-(01-03))
  - IBEC Branch: Puerto Rico: Office (Reel J-96, Card 708-12-01)
  - IBEC Branch: Puerto Rico: Procedure-Purchasing (Reel J-96, Card 708-15-(01-02))
  - IBEC Branch: Puerto Rico: Property-Equipment (Reel J-96, Card 708-17-(01-02))
  - IBEC Branch: Puerto Rico: Publicity (Reel J-95, Card 708-19-(01-10))
  - IBEC Branch: Puerto Rico: Staff (Reel J-96, Card 708-22-(01-05))
  - IBEC Branch: Puerto Rico: Staff-Unions (Reel J-96, Card 708-22-(01-03))
  - IBEC Branch: Puerto Rico: Taxes (Reel J-96, Card 708-24-(01-03))
  - IBEC Branch: Venezuela: Directors-Affiliated Companies (Card 702-06-01)
  - IBEC Branch: Venezuela: Finance (Card 702-07-(01-12))
  - IBEC Branch: Venezuela: Finance-Audits (Card 702-07-(01-02))
  - IBEC Branch: Venezuela: Finance-Bank Accounts (Card 702-07-(01-04))
  - IBEC Branch: Venezuela: Finance-Bank Accounts-Custody-National City (Card 702-07-01)
  - IBEC Branch: Venezuela: Finance-Bank Accounts- Safe Deposit (Card 702-07-01)
  - IBEC Branch: Venezuela: Finance-Budgets (Card 702-07-(01-02))
  - IBEC Branch: Venezuela: Finance-Consolidation- Shopping Centers (Card 702-07-(01-02))
  - IBEC Branch: Venezuela: Finance-Consolidation- Supermarkets (Reel J-92, Card 702-07-(01-09))
  - IBEC Branch: Venezuela: Finance-Financial Statements (Card 702-07-(01-03))
  - IBEC Branch: Venezuela: Finance-Foreign Exchange (Card 702-07-(01-05))
  - IBEC Branch: Venezuela: Finance-Loans (Card 702-07-01)
  - IBEC Branch: Venezuela: Investments (Card 702-10-01)
  - IBEC Branch: Venezuela: Legal (Card 702-11-01)
  - IBEC Branch: Venezuela: Legal-Counsel (Card 702-11-(01-02))
  - IBEC Branch: Venezuela: Legal-Counsel-Coles & Valera (Card 702-11-01)
  - IBEC Branch: Venezuela: Legal-Document-Agreement-Agency-General Foods (Card 702-11-01)
  - IBEC Branch: Venezuela: Legal-Documents-Agreement-Agency-International Paper (Card 702-11-01)
  - IBEC Branch: Venezuela: Legal-Documents-Contracts-Management (Card 702-11-01)
  - IBEC Branch: Venezuela: Legal-Documents-Leases (Card 702-11-01)
  - IBEC Branch: Venezuela: Office- Accounting & Service Division (Card 702-12-(01-02))
  - IBEC Branch: Venezuela: Office & Procedures (Card 702-12-01)
  - IBEC Branch: Venezuela: Office Space (Card 702-12-(01-02))
  - IBEC Branch: Venezuela: Organization- Policy &Administration (Card 702-12-01)
    Card mislabled, Organization-702-13
  - IBEC Branch: Venezuela: Public Relations (Card 702-18-(01-02))
  - IBEC Branch: Venezuela: Reports-Operations (Card 702-20-01)
  - IBEC Branch: Venezuela: Staff (Card 702-22-(01-02))
  - IBEC Branch: Venezuela: Staff A-Z (Card 702-22-(01-02))
  - IBEC Branch: Venezuela: Staff-Camp, John R. (Card 702-22-01)
  - IBEC Branch: Venezuela: Staff-Coles, William F. (Card 702-22-01)
  - IBEC Branch: Venezuela: Staff-Phillips, Louis A. (Card 702-22-01)
  - IBEC Branch: Venezuela: Staff-Taylor, Milton E. (Card 702-22-01)
  - IBEC Branch: Venezuela: Staff-Unions (Card 702-22-(01-03))
  - IBEC Branch: Venezuela: Taxes (Card 702-24-(01-08))
  - IBEC Foods Inc.: Finance (Reel J-135, Card 325-07-(01-11))
    Most cards are mislabled as 305-07.
  - IBEC Foods Inc.: New York: Associations-Brokers (Card 325-01-01)
  - IBEC Foods Inc.: New York: Directors (Card 325-06-(01-02))
  - IBEC Foods Inc.: New York: Finance-Customers-A & P (Card 325-07-01)